SERGEY RADKOV

Boise ID USA | (208) 371-3904 | radkovsn@gmail.com | www.sradkov.com

www.linkedin.com/in/radkovsn

https://github.com/eriixon

Permanent Work Authorization No Visa Sponsorship Required

TECHNOLOGIES

Proficiencies

C# Bootstrap
.NET Angular.js
ASP.NET Node.js
HTML / CSS NPM
JavaScript GitHub
jQuery Heroku

Microsoft SQL

RESTful Web services

Have experience with

MVC Pattern Java
Firebase Vue JS
none SQL React JS
API's Python

PROJECTS

Messenger Bot for Better Business Bureau

Facebook Messenger Bot is the back-end application for Better Business Bureau to find appropriate businesses through Facebook Messenger. In this project are used Node JS as back-end, BBB API (to look for find trustworthy businesses in North America), Google Maps API(to identify user location), the huge dictionary of US states/cities and Facebook Messenger Platform.

https://m.me/BBBSnakeRiverRegion

Quickbooks Helper Web Application

Self-Service customer updater tool. Allows a customer to enter their phone information and verify that they are a customer, and then allows the customer edit their name, address, and email information. This information is then updated into QuickBooks(tm) using the QuickBooks(tm) SDK.

https://gbemailgrabber.herokuapp.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Developer with a passion for online businesses has extensive knowledge of business analysis and substantial experience creating logical and innovative solutions to complex problems to increase efficiency, with 5+ years' telematics service promotion and 8 years' management experience.

EDUCATION

Back End with .NET C# Course

BoiseCodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2017

Web Development Immersive Full Stack Course

BoiseCodeWorks | Boise, Idaho | 2016 The leading premier coding bootcamp in Idaho.

Master's Degree | Transport Engineering Economics and Management

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 1997 – 2000

Bachelor's Degree | Transport Engineering Economics and Management

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 2000 – 2002 Russia's leading university in the field of management education.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Back-End Web Developer

Neoreef | Boise, Idaho | 09.2016 - now

Building reusable code and libraries for future use for the unique proprietary content management system, integration of user-facing elements developed by a front-end developers with server side logic.

Web Developer

Saharacase LLC | Boise, Idaho | 11.2016 - 09.2017

Co-developed a vibrant, secure website using interactive features and SEO best practices to optimize traffic, page views and the user experience (UX), developed product web templates for the main marketplaces (Amazon, eBay, Walmart, etc).

Web Developer

freelance | Boise, Idaho | 06.2016 - now

Created and maintained web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AngularJS and Node.js, optimized web pages for mobile.

Senior Product Engineer

Volvo Truck Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2010 -2015 A branch of Volvo Trucks, a global truck manufacturer.

Promoted Volvo telematics services, provided technical support for 600+ customers and 100+ team members, established new consulting service using Volvo's telematics.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Practical problem solver with exceptional attention to detail
- Strong presentation, communication and negotiation skills
- Demonstrated success in project and staff management
- Ability to adapt to rapidly changing environments